<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xslt" href="master.xslt"?>

<terms_and_conditions>

	
		<page_name>User Terms and Conditions</page_name>
	

	<tc>
			<title>
				No User Advertisement Agreement
			</title>
			<rules>
				Food Ninja is a growing cooking community of chefs. We are here to help others share 
				recipes and learn new things. We are not here for the personal benefit of your own personal
				businesses and products. Advertisements are strictly prohibited and will result in a ban for a week
				upon first warning. With each warning the ban time doubles.
			</rules>
	</tc>

	<tc>
			<title>
				One Account Agreement
			</title>
			<rules>
				Creating a second account on our site will result in the permanent banning of that account. Creating
				an account to circumvent a ban will result in both accounts and any future account being
				banned from this site permanently.
			</rules>
	</tc>
	
	<tc>
			<title>
				Anti-Harassment Measures
			</title>
			<rules>
				Even though there are no messaging services on this site you are still able to upload pictures
				and submit recipes. Submissions of photos of somebody else or "recipes" that harasses either
				another user or a non-user will result in a permanent ban. This is supposed to be a fun and friendly 
				site. Please keep things civil.
			</rules>
	</tc>
	
	
	
	<tc>
	
			<title>
				Terms Involving Harmful Recipes 
			</title>
			<rules>
				Recipes involving the user of substances that could cause severe harm or death are banned from
				this site. Posting such a recipe will result in a 6 month ban upon first offence and a permanent
				ban upon second effect. Spicy recipes should be given with a warning that they are hot and to beware.
			</rules>
			
			
	</tc>

	<tc>
	
			<title>
				Policy on Recipes Involving Drugs or Alcohol 
			</title>
			<rules>
				This is a family friendly site and doesn't allow the use of drugs or alcohol in recipes.
				Any recipes involving alcohol would be removed and will result in a warning upon
				first offence, a 2 day ban upon second offence and a week ban upon three or more offences.
				Food Ninja has a <bold_this>ZERO TOLERANCE</bold_this> policy for drugs.
				Any recipes involving drugs will result in the removal of that content and a permanent ban 
				from this site. 
			</rules>
	
	
	
	</tc>
	
	

	<tc>
	
			<title>
				Terms on Sexual Content
			</title>
			<rules>
				This is a family friendly site. This site is about learning how to cook and 
				sharing tips, tricks and recipes. As much as cooking is an art there's no place for sexual content here.
				Posting sexual or erotic material or recipes will result in the removal of that material and a two month ban. 
			</rules>
	
	
	</tc>
	
	
	<tc>
	
			<title>
				Terms on Non-Edible Recipes
			</title>
			<rules>
				As a food site we have a reputation to stick to food items. No recipes on how to make other things
				for crafts or anything else. Any anarchist cooking recipes or recipes on how to make bombs, explosive,
				fuels or poisons will result in a permanent ban along with the removal of those recipes.
			</rules>
	
	</tc>
	
	<tc>
			<title>
				Code of the Food Ninja Clan
			</title>
			
			<rules>
				 
				An honourable food ninja upholds the code to improve cooking and make food to the best of their
				abilities. They do their best to help their food ninja brethren to hone their cooking
				abilities. Until one day we all become grand master food ninjas and rejoice in Food Ninja Valhalla.
				We will be cooking for the food ninja gods and eating food of a taste which can not even be imagined 
				with our mortal forms. You're on the path to cooking enlightenment. Your food journey has begun.
				&lt;/br&gt; &lt;/br&gt;
				If you read up until this point you are now a member of the food ninja clan. As long as you follow
				our rules you should have lots of fun cooking and learning new recipes. Enjoy our site.
				&lt;/br&gt; &lt;/br&gt;
				If you didn't read our rules up until this point we now own your soul and all hope of you escaping 
				the food ninja underworld where you are forced to eat gram crackers on bread every day for eternity
				with no beverages while sitting around in a hot frying pan.
				
			</rules>
	</tc>

	
</terms_and_conditions>